const STORE = {
    questions: [
    {
      question:
       "The minimum age for a New York real estate broker's license?",
      choices: [
        '19',
        '18',
        '20',
        '21'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        '20'
    },
    {
      question:
        "A Salesperson’s license must be",
      choices: [
        'Displayed on the firm’s wall',
        'Kept in the salesperson’s wallet',
        'Retained by the principal broker',
        'Sent to the local realtors association'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Retained by the principal broker'
    },
    {
        question:
        "When a license is revoked, how long must a licensee wait before applying to have the license reinstated?",
        choices: [
            '18 months',
            '1 year',
            '6 months',
            '2 years'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        '1 year'
    },
    {
        question:
        "A deed is valid when it is",
        choices: [
            'Delivered and accepted',
            'Recorded',
            'Signed',
            'Notarized'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'Delivered and accepted'
    },
    {
        question:
        "A lien is an:",
        choices: [
            'Appurtenance',
            'Encroachment',
            'Encumbrance',
            'Eminent domain'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'Encumbrance'
    },
    {
        question:
        "Broker John Brown owes customer Susie Smith",
        choices: [
            'Loyalty',
            'Fairness and Honesty',
            'Confidentiality',
            'Accounting'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'Fairness and Honesty'
    },
    {
        question:
        "Salesperson need not be",
        choices: [
            'Licensed by the state',
            'At least 18 years old',
            'Already experienced in real estate',
            'Supervised by a broker'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'Already experienced in real estate'
    },
    {
        question:
        "When serving as a buyer's agent, according to the Civil Code sections dealing with agency, a licensee owes a fidicuary duty:",
        choices: [
            'The buyer',
            'The Seller',
            'The broker',
            'The buyer & seller'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'The buyer'
    },
    {
        question:
        "In a real estate transaction, fiduciary duties are owed to the:",
        choices: [
            'Principal',
            'Customer',
            'Broker',
            'Agent'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'Principal'
    },
    {
        question:
        "If a salesperson acts as an independent contractor, then:",
        choices: [
            'He controls his own working hours',
            'All of his listing belongs to him',
            'His broker must withold income tax from his commission checks',
            'He is responsible to his broker as to how his work is performed'
        ],
        correctAnswer:
        'He controls his own working hours'
    }
],
currentQuestion: 0,
score: 0,
};